{
    "subject": "resource/Nathan_Douglas",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Nathan James Douglas (born 4 December 1982 in Oxford) is an English athlete who specialises in the triple jump. He won the silver medal at the 2006 European Athletics Championships in Gothenburg with a jump of 17.21 metres. He suffered a major injury in 2007 and, although he managed to compete at the 2008 Beijing Olympics, he struggled to find form as the injury had upset his technique.His personal best is 17.64 m (57 ft 101\u20444 in), set in 2005.",
    "human_readable": "Nathan Douglas is an English athlete who specialises in the triple jump.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8397005200386047,
            "question": "Is Nathan Douglas a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7243691682815552,
            "question": "Who are some other well-known athletes in the same sport as Nathan Douglas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.684800922870636,
            "question": "What sport does Nathan Douglas specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.593430757522583,
            "question": "What event within his sport is Nathan Douglas known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46631988883018494,
            "question": "What is the significance of the triple jump in athletics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44001370668411255,
            "question": "Does Nathan Douglas participate in any other sporting events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4209671914577484,
            "question": "What are some of Nathan Douglas's notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3632831871509552,
            "question": "What is Nathan Douglas's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19310404360294342,
            "question": "Has Nathan Douglas won any major championships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15409314632415771,
            "question": "Where does Nathan Douglas train?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nathan Douglas is an English athlete who specialises in the triple jump.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4984_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Nathan Douglas won any major championships?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4984_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Nathan Douglas's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4984_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Nathan Douglas's notable achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4984_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4984_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of whether the statement about Nathan Douglas is supported:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Nathan Douglas, confirming that he is indeed an English athlete specializing in the triple jump. This aligns with the statement provided in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}